// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is PHP?",
    answer: "All of the mentioned",
    options: [
      "PHP is an open-source programming language",
      "PHP is used to develop dynamic and interactive websites",
      "PHP is a server-side scripting language",
      "All of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Who is the father of PHP?",
    answer: "Rasmus Lerdorf",
    options: [
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      "Drek Kolkevi",
      "Willam Makepiece",
      "List Barely"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What does PHP stand for?",
    answer: "PHP stands for Hypertext Preprocessor",
    options: [
      "PHP stands for Preprocessor Home Page",
      "PHP stands for Pretext Hypertext Processor",
      "PHP stands for Personal Hyper Processor",
      "PHP stands for Hypertext Preprocessor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is the default file extension of PHP files?",
    answer: ".php",
    options: [
      ".php",
      ".ph",
      ".xml",
      ".html"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which is the right way of declaring a variable in PHP?",
    answer: "$_hello",
    options: [
      "$3hello",
      "$this",
      "$_hello",
      "$5_Hello"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following PHP functions can be used for generating unique ids?",
    answer: "uniqueid()",
    options: [
      "id()",
      "mdid()",
      "md5()",
      "uniqueid()"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "A function in PHP which starts with __ (double underscore) is known as __________",
    answer: "Magic Function",
    options: [
      "Magic Function",
      "Default Function",
      "nbuilt Function",
      "User Defined Function"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many functions does PHP offer for searching and modifying strings using Perl-compatible regular expressions.",
    answer: "8",
    options: [
      "10",
      "7",
      "8",
      "9"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which one of the following PHP function is used to determine a fileâ€™s last access time?",
    answer: " fileatime()",
    options: [
      "fileatime()",
      "filetime()",
      "fileltime()",
      "filectime()"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The developers of PHP deprecated the safe mode feature as of which PHP version?",
    answer: "PHP 5.3.0",
    options: [
      "PHP 5.3.1",
      "PHP 5.3.0",
      "PHP 5.2.0",
      "PHP 5.1.0"
    ]
  },
  
];